This is the GHQ's Public Information Division.
[ﾏｲｸ]（アナウンス）こちらは
ＧＨＱ広報部です。→
In accordance with Article 9 Section 3
of the Infection Control Law,
現在　防疫法　第９条３項に基づく
都市隔離宣言を発令中。→
an emergency city quarantine is now in effect.
環状七号線から外への移動は
固く禁じられています。
Citizens are strictly prohibited
from venturing outside Loop 7.
（集）《あれから２週間》
It's been two weeks since then.
Tokyo has completely changed.
《東京は
すっかり変わってしまった》
That incident two weeks ago...
《２週間前の事件…》
《ロストクリスマスの再来
といわれた→
The mass Apocalypse Virus outbreak some
called "the second coming of Lost Christmas"
アポカリプスウイルス
大感染のため　都心は封鎖された》
has the city center blockaded off.
《ネットや電話は通じなくなり→
Internet and phone lines are down,
and the TVand radio stations have gone silent.
テレビもラジオも沈黙したまま》
"Vaccination Station"
The people are living in groups
at local evacuation sites.
《人々は　各地の避難所に集まって暮らしている》
"Haruka Ouma"
"Dialing"
《ここ　天王洲第一高校には
自然と生徒たちが集まってきた》
Students have automatically gathered
here at Tennozu First High School.
《家族と連絡もつかず→
"Calls Currently Limited"
"Please wait."
They can't contact their families
封鎖地区外に　自宅があるせいで
帰れなくなり→
and they can't go home because
they live outside the blockade zone,
そのまま
ここで暮らしているのだ》
so they've just been staying here.
《ＧＨＱのアナウンスは→
The GHQ announcements say the
blockades will be lifted any moment.
「封鎖は　間もなく解除される」
と言っている》
《谷尋あたりは
疑っているみたいだけど…》
Some people, like Yahiro, seem to doubt that...
《僕は　こんな状況
長くは続かないと思ってる》
But I don't think these conditions will last long.
Shu.
≪（いのり）集。
（いのり）また　ここにいたの？
（集）うん。
You're here again?
Yeah.
（集）何となくね。
My feet just take me here.
《もう　全部
終わったんだよね…。　涯》
It's... all over now, isn't it, Gai?
♪♪～
A symphony of disintegration resounds
The falling rain has the exact timbre of tears
Realize
Those eyes are for recognizing each other with
Those voices are for
conveying our feelings with
Those hands are for joining
hands with our loved ones
All you living beings who can hear this song
The truth lies within your heart
And even when you're traveling a stormy sea
It will give you a strength
That will never flinch
School
（綾瀬）うっ…。→
あっ！
Ow...
（綾瀬）痛ーっ。
（綾瀬）何やってるのよ　私。
What am I even doing?
A little rowdy, aren't you?
（難波）穏やかじゃないね。→
You okay? Can you stand?
大丈夫？　立てる？
消えて！
Get lost.
Don't get so up in arms.
（難波）そんなに警戒しないでよ。
（数藤）手伝ってあげようって
だけじゃない。
We're just offering to help.
頼んでない！
I didn't ask you.
Oh, you're one of those
"I can do it myself" types, huh?
（数藤）あ～　君は　あれだ。
１人で　できるもん的な？
どっか行って！
Go away!
What, you only sweet to your honey?
（数藤）何？
ツンデレちゃんなの？　君。
（難波）克己心は　いいけど
親切を無にされるとムカつくよね。
Nothing wrong with being stoic,
but it pisses me off when somebody
doesn't appreciate my kindness.
仲良くしようぜ。
ほら。
Let's be friendly here, okay?
ちょっと　やめなよ。
Hey, stop it.
（数藤）何だ？　お前。
What's your deal?
No, what are you doing?
And to a girl who fell down, too.
君こそ　何してるの？
倒れてる子に向かって。
こんな状況だからね。　助け合いの
精神を発揮してたんだよ。
We were demonstrating a spirit of
cooperation in this time of trouble.
Yup! There a problem with that?
だぜ。
何か問題ある？
Missile Kick!
（鶫）ミサイルゥゥ　キーック！！
（数藤）うわっ！
えっ！？
What the hell was that for?!
何するんだ　君！
何すんの！
What was that for?
それは　こっちのせりふよ！
You tell me! What are you doing to Aya? Pervs!
あんたたちこそ
綾姉に何してんのさ！　ど変態！
- Hey, don't lump me in with...
- Piss off, shrimp!
ちょっと　僕まで　いっしょくたに…。
（数藤）ざけんなよ　ちび！
ネイ！
発展途上中よ！
Nay! I'm just getting started!
（難波）おい。
Hey.
（数藤）チッ！
（数藤）覚えてろよ！
（鶫）冗談！→
You'll regret this!
Yeah, right! Like I'd waste a single
millibyte storing this memory!
そんな記憶に　１マイクロミリバイトだって
使うもんか！　ベェーっだ！
Bleh!
大丈夫？
（綾瀬）うん。
All right?
Yeah.
何かあったの？
Did something happen?
Nah, they just hassled me a little.
別に。
ちょっと絡まれただけ。
ねえ　もう行ってくれない？
えっ　でも…。
Say, would you mind leaving?
But...
前に言ったよね。
人の手は借りない。→
I told you before, didn't I?
I never get help from anyone.
よじ登る姿は
エレガントじゃないって。
I don't look elegant crawling up into it!
行こ　集。
うん。
Let's go, Shu.
Right...
ありゃ　相当　参ってるなー。
やっぱり。
She's in pretty bad shape.
That figures...
涯のこと
一番ショックなの綾姉だから。
Gai's death hit Aya the hardest.
I wonder if Funeral Parlor
will close up shop now...
これで　葬儀社も
店じまいかなぁ…。
《葬儀社のみんなとは
あの事件で　はぐれてしまった》
We got separated from the other
members when all that happened.
《ほとんどの仲間は
行方知れずの中→
We don't know where
most of our other people are,
綾瀬と鶫だけが　生徒に紛れて
ここに避難している》
but Ayase and Tsugumi are blending in
with the students and taking shelter here.
《そして　涯は　もう　いない…》
And Gai... is gone.
（花音）物資は　供奉院グループが
空輸してくれていることもあって→
The Kuhouin Group is airlifting supplies in,
so we're still in pretty good shape there.
まだ　かなりの余裕がありますね。
（花音）ワクチンが
少し　心もとないですけど…。
I'm a little worried about
our vaccine stores, though...
（谷尋）ウイルスの影響も
気になる。
The effects of the virus are a concern, too.
I'd like to secure a good stock.
Can we ask for your help?
（谷尋）ストックは確保しておきたい。
お願いできますか？
（亞里沙）分かったわ。
おじいさまに掛け合ってみましょう。
All right. I'll try to negotiate
something with my grandfather.
（颯太）気にし過ぎじゃねえの？
Aren't you worrying too much?
封鎖だって
そこまで長引かないだろ？
The quarantine won't last that long.
We can't afford to be overoptimistic.
楽観は禁物だ。　事件から２週間
緊張の糸が切れる時期だ。→
It's been two weeks.
That's about when people start losing it.
It sounds like there's already
been a small riot in Shinjuku.
新宿でも　ちょっとした暴動が
あったらしいし。
He has a point... we've been
seeing fights inside the school, too.
確かに。　校内でも
もめ事が目に付くわよね。
（祭）みんな疲れてるんだよ。
帰りたくても帰れない子も多いし。
It's because everyone's tired.
There are a lot of kids who
want to go home and can't.
せめて　息抜きとか
できればいいんだけど…。
If we could at least give them
a breather, that would help...
うん？　そういえば…。
Come to think of it!
What is it, Souta?
どうしたの？　颯太。
Say... how about we do a Culture Festival?
なあ　文化祭やらないか？
はあ？
Huh?
"Candied Apples"
（颯太）ホントなら
今月　文化祭じゃん！→
Normally we'd be having
the Culture Festival this month, right?
Come on, let's do it!
なあ　やろうぜ　文化祭！
Are you kidding?
We're in the middle of a crisis.
何　言ってるんだ　お前！
この非常時に。
だからこそだよ！
That's exactly why we should!
Let's liven things up with something big
一発　ドカンと盛り上げて
嫌～な空気を吹き飛ばそうぜ！
and clear out the bad atmosphere in this place!
（亞里沙）
いいアイデアかもしれないわ。
That might be a good idea.
（谷尋）えっ！　会長まで…。
You too, President?
We have enough food to last us a good while.
（亞里沙）食料は　当面　心配ないし
ささやかなものならやれると思う。
I think we can pull off
something if we keep it small.
You heard the lady!
（颯太）先輩の言うとおりだぜ。
もっと　空気を読みたまえよ
寒川官房長官。
Read the social atmosphere,
Chief Cabinet Secretary Samukawa.
ホントに大丈夫ですか？
Is this really okay?
こんな状態は　もうすぐ終わるわ。
心配無用よ。
Not to worry. These conditions will end soon.
っていうなら…。
（祭）いいよね。
In that case...
Then it's okay, right?
ねっ　集。
そうだね。
Right, Shu?
Yeah.
（嘘界）ほう。
いよいよですか。
Ah, it's finally time?
Yes, Sir. They said we'd have
approval within a few days.
（ローワン）はっ。
数日以内には承認されると。
（嘘界）それまでは退屈ですねー。
ちょっと　つまみ食いしましょうか。
Life will be boring until then...
Shall we have a little advance taste?
Please, Sir, no pranks!
（ローワン）悪ふざけは
おやめください。→
以前とは立場が違うのですよ。
嘘界局長。
Your position isn't what it was before...
...Chief Segai.
Goodness... We've both landed
in difficult positions, haven't we?
（嘘界）いやぁ　難儀な立場に
なっちゃいましたね　お互い。
（ローワン）まったくです。
I couldn't agree more.
（谷尋）お前まで賛同するとはな。
うん…。
I didn't expect you to agree.
何か　僕も
騒ぎたい気分だったのかも。
I guess maybe I felt like living it up, too.
（谷尋）こいつが
俺の中にあったのか…。→
So this was inside me?
Why are you able to hand it to me all of a sudden?
どうして
急に手渡せるようになった？
この間の戦いのとき　能力が
何か変化したみたいなんだ。
During that last fight,
my powers changed, I think.
戻すには？
また　離してみて。
How do we put it back?
Try letting go of it again.
あっ。
These "Voids" are just one
mystery after another, aren't they?
（谷尋）つくづく　謎だらけだな
ヴォイドってやつは。
うん…。　でも　何で　突然
ヴォイドが気になったの？
Uh-huh... But why are you
suddenly so interested in Voids?
Curiosity.
（谷尋）好奇心さ。
Well, I don't think I'll be
using this power again, though.
まあ　こんな力
もう使うことはないと思うけど。
（谷尋）本当に　そう思うのか？
Do you really think that?
どういうこと？
What do you mean?
These conditions can't last long.
こんな状態が
長く続くわけがない。
And by that I mean the opposite
of what Kuhouin does, Shu.
俺が言ってるのは
供奉院とは逆の意味だぞ　集。→
お前の右手　その能力…。
Your right hand, its power...
出番は
そう遠くないように思えるな。
I doubt the time to use them is far off.
（花音）わ…　私は　いいから！
I-I don't need those!
Oh, don't say that. Here you go!
（鶫）そんなこと言わずにー。
ほれほれ。
あっ　集！
ジャジャーン！
Hey, Shu!
Ta-da!
どうしたの？　その格好。
（鶫）アニマル喫茶だって。
What's the outfit for?
They told me this was an Animal Café!
すっかり　なじんでるね　鶫。
You're totally part of the school
crowd now, aren't you, Tsugumi?
くよくよしてても仕方なし。
せっかくだから　楽しみませんと！
Well, moping won't help anyone.
We have to take this
opportunity to have some fun!
But I don't have anything to do with it!
私は関係ないのに。
（谷尋）アハッ。
Don't laugh.
笑わないでよ！
Sorry, sorry. They look good on you.
悪い　悪い。
似合ってるよ。
もう…。
Sheesh...
そういえば　いのりは？
Say, where's Inori?
Hey, Shu! Over here!
≪（颯太）おーい　集！
こっち　こっち！
A live Egoist concert?
ＥＧＯＩＳＴの生ライブ！？
It's the festival's main event!
（颯太）
文化祭のメーンイベントさ！
（颯太）演出は　俺に任せてくれよ！
Leave the stage directing to me!
魂館文部科学大臣の実力
見せてやるぜ！
I, Tamadate, Minister of Education,
Culture, Sports, Science and Technology,
will show you what I'm made of!
いのりは　いいの？
うん。
Are you okay with this, Inori?
やってみたいの　私が。
いい？
I want to try it.
Okay?
もちろん。
楽しみだよ。
Of course. I look forward to it.
（ダリル）まったく…。→
Come on, a festival now?
There's something wrong with these people.
こんなときに　お祭りなんて
どうかしてるよ。
（ダリル）脳みそにまで　ばい菌
回ってんじゃないの　こいつら。
Maybe the germs have spread to their brains.
ホッホッホッホ！
（ダリル）あっ！
（鶫）うわっ！　うおっとっと！
That hurt! What if I'd been injured?!
痛いなー！　ケガしたら
どうすんのさ！　気を付けてよね。
Be more careful.
あー　ごめん　ごめん。
でも　ちょうどよかった。
Oh, sorry! But hey, perfect timing!
Here, you take this.
はい　君。　これ持って。
（ダリル）うっ！　ちょっと！
Hey! Why should I have to...
何で　僕が…。
（鶫）これも　お願い。　これも。
This too, please. And this!
ハァ…。　どうして　僕が
こんな野蛮な仕事を！
Why should I have to do barbaric work like this?
Man, you're a weakling.
（鶫）もやし子だなぁ　君は。
お前が　次から次へと
押し付けるからだろ！
No, you just overloaded me!
まーまー！
これで　機嫌を直したまえよ。
Aw, take this and cheer up.
What is it?
何？　これ。
（鶫）お駄賃。
Your reward.
I don't want that yucky food.
いらないよ！
こんな　ばっちい食べ物！
When someone does something nice for you...
人の好意は
素直に受け取りなさい！
...shut up and accept it!
（ダリル）うわっ！　や…　やめて！
（鶫）ホーッホッホッホ！
St-Stop it!
"Animal Café"
Whoa, Shinomiya, you're good at this!
（祭）わっ　篠宮さん　上手！
You can call me Ayase.
（綾瀬）綾瀬で　いいですよ。
校条さんでしたっけ？
Your name is Menjo, right?
Please, call me Hare. I'm sorry for
asking you to do this out of the blue.
（祭）私のことも
祭って呼んでください。→
急に　お願いしちゃって
ごめんなさい。
でも　どうして　私を？
Why me, though?
やっぱり　１人で
寂しそうに見えちゃったかな。
I suppose I looked lonely by myself?
（祭）違いますよ。
No.
あの…　最近　集
変わったんですよね　いい方に。
Um, Shu's changed lately,
you know? In a good way.
I just thought that must be thanks
to all of you in Funeral Parlor.
きっと　葬儀社の皆さんの
おかげなんだろうなって。→
So I wanted to say thank you.
だから
お礼が言いたかったんです。→
ありがとうございました。
Thank you very much.
（ダリル）
えっ？　ああ　そうだよ。→
Huh? Yeah, that's right.
Inori Yuzuriha, Shu Ouma... everyone's here.
楪いのり。　桜満　集。
みんな　いたよ。
回りくどいなぁ。
This is pointlessly complicated.
こんな場所
さっさと　つぶしちゃえばいいのに。
You could just crush this place now!
No, that won't do. We're in the
middle of deliberations right now.
（嘘界）そうは　いきません。
今は審議の真っ最中。→
私たちは　直接　動けないのです。
直接はね。→
We can't make any direct moves.
No direct ones...
とにかく　手出しは無用です。→
At any rate, don't interfere.
I trust you understand?
分かりましたね？
（ダリル）「はいよ」
Yeah, got it.
What is this thing? It looks so cheap.
何だよ　この貧乏くさい食べ物。
The next time I see that runt,
I swear I'm gonna torment her.
あの　ちんちくりん！
今度　会ったら　絶対　いじめてやる。
≪（花火の音）
（生徒たち）いらっしゃーい！
"Happy Tenno Festival!"
"Times like this, we have to have fun!"
[ﾏｲｸ]（亞里沙）ただ今より
天王祭を開催いたします。→
We are now officially opening the Tenno Festival.
Have all the fun you like, everyone.
皆さん
心ゆくまで　お楽しみください。
"Operations"
This is fun, huh Aya!
楽しいね　綾姉。→
私たちも　普通に学校行ってたら
こういうこと　してたのかなぁ。→
I wonder if we'd be doing this too,
if we went to school like normal kids.
ねえ　どう思う？
What do you think?
あ…。
（鶫）あっ　ベビーカステラ！
Look, mini-hotcakes!
綾姉　ベビーカステラだよ。
ウフッ！
It's mini-hotcakes, Aya!
文化祭やってんぞ。
（暴徒）許せねえな。
They're havin' a Cultural Festival.
That ain't right. Not when times
are tough and there's people starvin'!
物がなくて苦しんでる人が
大勢いるご時世によ。
You said it!
≪（暴徒）そのとおりだ！→
こういうときこそ→
This is a job for the Warmhearted
Men Gang. Am I right?
俺たち　まごころ青年団の出番だ。
そうだろう？
ハンヴィーに　エンドレイヴ　ゴーチェ…。
本物？
A Humvee and a Gautier Endlave?
Are they the real thing?
どうしたんだ？　それ！
How'd you get those?!
もらった。
（暴徒）「もらった」
- A gift.
ホントか？　おい！
Whoa, are you serious?!
（暴徒）
「俺らに賛同する資産家だって」→
He said he was a wealthy man
who agreed with our cause.
「ちょっと怪しかったけど
でも　いい人だったよ」
Seemed a little sketchy,
but he turned out to be a good guy.
"Good guy"?
いい人って…。
Just goes to show the high hopes
people have for our justice!
（暴徒）それだけ　俺らの正義が
期待されてるってことだろ。→
さあ　行こうぜ！→
Come on, let's go!
We're gonna teach those over-happy
school kids what a harsh world this is!
浮かれた学生たちに
世間の厳しさを教えてやるんだ！
You sure you don't want any?
These are really good.
ホントに　いらないの？
おいしいよ　これ。
あのさ…。
（鶫）あっ！　綾姉。　ラスイチさんだよ。
- Say...
- Hey, Aya, this is the last one! Here... say "ah."
ほら　あ～ん。
（綾瀬）やめて！
Stop it!
何するの？
（綾瀬）ねえ　何で切ったの！
What was that for?
Hey, why did you cut it?
Huh? What do you mean?
えっ？　何のこと？
Why did you cut my connection that day?!
（綾瀬）あのとき
何で接続を切ったの！？→
私　まだ　やれたのに！
涯を守れたのに！
I could have kept going!
I could have protected Gai!
（鶫）そんな…。　じゃあ　綾姉が
死んじゃっても　よかったわけ？
That's crazy... What, so you
wouldn't have minded if you'd died?
死んだ方が　よかったわよ！→
I wish I'd died!
If my survival is so half-baked...
こんな…
中途半端に生き残って…。→
事故のときも　今も。
After the accident, and now, too...
そんなこと言うの　やめてよ。
こっちが悲しくなるじゃん。
Don't say things like that.
You're gonna make me sad.
ごめんね　綾姉。
私　戻るね。
I'm sorry, Aya. I'll go back to the festival.
（颯太）それで　音楽が鳴るけど→
And then the music will start,
but don't come out yet, okay?
そこでは　まだ出ないで。
うん。
合図したら　出て。
分かった。
Come out on my signal.
Okay.
（綾瀬）《あの子には歌がある》→
She has her songs.
《私とは違う》→
She's not like me.
《エンドレイヴを失った
私なんかとは…》
I'm just some girl who lost her Endlave...
Ayase.
綾瀬。
あっ　集…。
Shu...
What are you doing over here?
何で　こんな所に？
もっと近くに来ないの？
Don't you want to come closer?
There's no point.
I can't be useful for anything anyway.
いいの　私は。
何の役にも立てないし。
Nobody said anything about that.
そんなこと
言ってないじゃない。
仲間なんだからさ
もっと一緒に…。
I'm saying you're one of us,
so you should be with us more...
涯は死んだのよ！？
Gai died, you know!
違う…。
守れなかったのよ。
No... I couldn't protect him.
私が　あの人を死なせてしまった。
I let him die.
違うよ　綾瀬。
涯を死なせたのは僕だ。
You're wrong, Ayase.
I'm the one who let him die.
It was me.
僕なんだよ。
≪（衝撃音）
あっ！
（生徒たちの悲鳴）
エンドレイヴ！
An Endlave!
（銃声）
ハッハー！　ビンゴ！
Bingo!
ここにまで暴動が！？
（谷尋）違う。　あれは軍用だ！
The riots have reached us, too?!
No. That's a military machine!
Dammit! What the hell is this about?!
くそっ！
何なんだよ　いったい！
Where's Shu?
集は？
Hey!
ちょっと！
君が戦う必要はない。
There's no need for you to fight!
Let's get you somewhere safe!
ひとまず　安全な所へ。
逃げたくなんかないの！
私の接続を切らないで！！
But I don't want to run away!
Don't cut my connection!
うわっ！
What are you doing?
何やってるんだ！
あっ。
Ayase...
綾瀬…。
大丈夫？
あんたも私を怠け者にしたいの！？
- Are you okay?
- You want to make me a slacker, too?!
そんな…。
No, I...
Gai gave me legs.
涯は私に足をくれたの。
どこまでも速く　高く駆ける足を。
Legs that could run fast anywhere, any height.
But I...
なのに　私は…！
無理だよ。
私は終われないよ。
It's no good! I can't end now!
お願い　集。
私を１人で立たせて！
Please, Shu. Let me stand on my own!
Everyone head for the old university building!
（亞里沙）皆さん　旧大学棟の方へ！≪（祭）キャッ！
（ハンヴィーの走行音）
≪（祭）キャー！
（亞里沙）校条さん！
Menjo!
えっ？
これ　私のヴォイドなの。
This is my Void.
Pretty sweet, huh?
いいでしょ？
（祭）はい！
Yes!
Gai, I'm moving forward too.
Even if you're not here, I'll go forward!
《涯！　私も進みます。
あなたが　いなくても　前に！》
What the hell was that?
何だよ！？　さっきの！
（暴徒）知るか！
How should I know?
She's...
（暴徒）こいつ…！
（綾瀬）ベェーっ！
Bleh!
（暴徒）うわっ！
（暴徒）うっ…。　クソっ！
Shit...
撃つぞ　ホントに！
I'll shoot you! For real!
（鶫）「御用だ　御用だ！」
You're under arrest!
うわっ！
Go, Aya!
（鶫）「綾姉。　行って！」
（綾瀬）うん！
Right!
See, you were useful.
役に立ったでしょ。
Dammit, what the hell is this?!
（暴徒）「だあああ！
何だってんだよー！！」
Shu!
集！
うおぉぉぉ！！
♪♪～
（生徒たちの歓声）
♪ Blooming wildflower ♪
♪♪「咲いた　野の花よ」
♪ I beg you, please tell me ♪
♪♪「ああ　どうか　おしえておくれ
人は何故…」
- ♪ Why do people fight and hurt each other? ♪
- It's been a long time since
I ran full-tilt on my own legs like that.
- ♪ Why do people fight and hurt each other? ♪
（綾瀬）久々に　自分の足で
全力疾走したわ。
気持ち良かった。
- It felt good.
- ♪ Why do people fight and hurt each other? ♪
僕も　ちょっと吹っ切れたよ。
- I feel a little better, too.
- ♪ Why do people fight and hurt each other? ♪
変に難しく
考えてただけなのかも。
- Maybe I was just over-complicating
things in my head before.
- ♪ Why do people fight and hurt each other? ♪
涯のことは
まだ割り切れないけど→
I can't accept what happened to Gai yet,
それでも　少しずつ
考えていこうと思う。→
but even so, I want to think
it through little by little.
私に何ができるかを。
うん。　僕もだよ。
To think about what I can do.
Me too.
ありがとう　集。
Thanks, Shu.
（拍手・歓声）
Hey, everybody! The TV's back on!
（颯太）みんな！
テレビが映るようになったって！
モニターに映像を回してと。
And transferring the feed to the monitors...
（生徒たち）わあ！
（茎道）「その調査の結果…」
えっ？
In that investigation,
we were unable to find any
survivors in the area within Loop 7
（茎道）「環状七号線より内側には→
重度のキャンサー患者以外に
生存者は確認されず→
who weren't highly cancerous.
臨時政府とＧＨＱは
救助活動を打ち切り→
The provisional government and GHQ
have agreed to cease rescue operations
今後１０年にわたり
完全封鎖することで合意しました」
and completely seal off
the area for the next ten years.
環七って…。
（生徒）ここも　そうだろ。
Loop 7?
- But we're inside Loop 7!
- What?
えっ　何？
（茎道）「われわれは→
We will devote our utmost efforts
to eradicating the Apocalypse Virus
国際社会の懸念を払拭すべく→
and thereby dispelling the concerns
of the international community.
アポカリプスウイルス撲滅に
尽力する所存です」→
I believe that a total purification
in order to bring about new birth
「再生のための浄化。　それこそが
このたび　日本国　臨時政府の→
is my duty as the newly inaugurated
President of Japan's provisional government.
大統領に就任した
この私の責務と信じます」
What the hell is going on?!
何なんだよ…　これって！
What am I supposed to care about,
left behind alone in a world like that?
♪♪～
I spent so many days,
accumulated so many feelings
And you were by my side the whole time,
A fixture of my life, and when you left,
I discovered their weight for the first time
If I'd gripped your hand tight
that day and not let go...
In the end, I was only living
in my own self-satisfied world
"Now it's like I'm a liar
for saying I did it all for you"
Even those murmured words don't reach you
Run, run to you
Watch, I'll fall as often,
get lost as often as it takes
Wait for me, because I'm on my way
No matter what difficulties are waiting there